/**
 * Identifies chunks based on labels that uses IOB like encoding
 * Assumes labels have the form <tag>-<type>
 *  where the tag is a prefix indicating where in the chunk it is.
 * Supports various encodings: IO, IOB, IOE, BILOU, SBEIO, []
 * The type is
 * Example:  Bill   works for  Bank   of     America
 * IO:       I-PER  O     O    I-ORG  I-ORG  I-ORG
 * IOB1:     B-PER  O     O    B-ORG  I-ORG  I-ORG
 * IOB2:     I-PER  O     O    B-ORG  I-ORG  I-ORG
 * IOE1:     E-PER  O     O    I-ORG  I-ORG  E-ORG
 * IOE2:     I-PER  O     O    I-ORG  I-ORG  E-ORG
 * BILOU:    U-PER  O     O    B-ORG  I-ORG  L-ORG
 * SBEIO:    S-PER  O     O    B-ORG  I-ORG  E-ORG
 * @author Angel Chang
 */
